

Mikhail Pogretskiy

Rust developer

Profile

Software developer with passion for building reliable and efficient software, experienced with Rust. blockchain. I love collaborating with other developers to discuss various approaches to complex problems to provide the best solution and learn from other people's experiences.

Employment history

Smart contract developer (Rust) at Bictory

January 2022 - October 2022

Remote

Rust WASM Concordium

Designing, implementing, documenting and integrating WASM smart contracts in Concordium ecosystem.

Optimizing the size of WASM modules.

Blockchain developer (Rust) at Gear

August 2021 - December 2021

Moscow, Russia

Rust Substrate

Developing and maintaining Gear, a Substrate smart contract platform for Polkadot

Creating smart contract library API

Extending smart contract test library

Blockchain developer (Rust) at XDSoft

September 2019 - March 2021

Novosibirsk, Russia

Rust Tokio GitLab CI

Developing Exonum blockchain framework fork with private transactions and GOST cryptography

Translating business requirements to granular tasks

Creating automation scripts and setting up GitLab CI

Creating tasks, distributing them to team members, reviewing code and maintaining documentation

Contacts

E-mail

mikhail.pogretskiy@gmail.com

Telegram

@Anfid

Mobile

+995 (595) 46 56 29

Date/Place of birth

22.07.1997, Russia

Website

Anfid.github.io

Links

Anfid

Programming languages

Rust

Elm

Lua C

Skills

*NIX

Git

WASM

x86 ASM

Languages

Russian	Native
English	Fluent

Embedded developer (C/C++) at MERA

March 2018 - September 2019

Nizhniy Novgorod, Russia

C/C++ Embedded Networks RTOS

Developing and maintaining Linux and RTOS embedded security systems

Improving device network connection stability

Education

Nizhniy Novgorod Technical College

October 2013 - October 2017

Nizhniy Novgorod, Russia